Ms. Crockett, I do agree with you about Tyree Nichols' death.
I watched the video and it was tragic and extremely difficult to watch.
I would also like to point out that that city is Democrat-controlled
and the five officers that have been arrested and charged are black.
And I think that this isn't an issue of racism or anything like that.
I think that the judge and the jury in the trial needs to work out what happened there.
But I share that with you.
But I'd like to also point something that I'd hope you share with me.
There's a woman in this room whose daughter was murdered on January 6th, Ashley Babbitt.
And Ashley Babbitt has, there's never been a trial.
As a matter of fact, no one has cared about the person that shot and killed her.
And no one in this Congress has really addressed that issue.
January 6th committee didn't address it.